southeastnow.com 2018-10-23

# Bollywood Charcha

## **Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting our website, we appreciate your trust with us. The submission of your personal information is not at all required in order to browse website but there can be changes in the policies. To stay updated keep checking. By browsing over our website you assure that you accept all the privacy policies described in this notice. 

**What information do we obtain?  **

  *   Automatic Information: We receive and store several types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, many websites use “Cookies” and obtain a certain type of information when you access the website on the web browser or other content served by on behalf of the website on other websites. 
  *   The information you provide us: We store any information that you enter on our website. We use the information just to respond to your requests, improving our website and communication with you. 
  *   Other websites links: The content on this website may contain links to other external websites. 

**What are cookies?  **

While using an internet browser to visit or surf any website typically small text files can place themselves in your computer as browser’s history or program data subfolders which are called Cookies. A cookie can be of two types- the first is which expires when you close the browser and the second stays in your computer until you delete it manually. So like another company our readers will get cookies by us or by companies which are running their ads on our website. Cookies can help us and advertisers to analyze and identify users on our website and it also helps us to serve content to match your preferences. 

**Do we share your personal information?**  

Information about our users is very important for us and we do not disclose that information to someone else. We only share it in the following instances:

  *   In order to take any action against suspected illegal activities/ violation of the our terms and provisions  
  *   To implement or entail terms and conditions and privacy policies
  *   To protect our character, assets and our rights/ rights of third party and personal safety of the users  
  *   We may also disclose personal information if it is required by the law to do so in a good belief because it is necessary to disclose such info to counter court orders or miscellaneous legal processes. 
  *   In case of transferring or selling the website to other company user’s info will be transferred too. 

**Policy update:**

In any case, if we make the change or update our privacy policy or its provisions we will inform you by posting on our page/website so keep in check about our updated policies.

**Google Analytics  **

We use Google Analytics to track visitors on this site. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect this data.In order to be compliant with the new regulation Google included a data processing amendment.The data we collect will be processed anonymously and “Data sharing” is disabled.We don’t use other Google services in combination with Google Analytics cookies. 

If you have any concern about privacy please send us a mail at….so that we can help you with the problem.
